Guide to the Biographical Reference Collection, 1972-2004 UA.01.11.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Biographical Reference collection
1972 - 2004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. University Archives
UA.01.11.0004
15 Linear Feet
The Biographical Reference Collection contains files of clippings, publications, biographical sketches, curriculum vitae, and other materials about the activities of Duke University administration, faculty, staff, and alumni, as well as other people connected or associated with the University, including members of the Duke family. These files were compiled from a variety of sources by University Archives staff for use in reference and research. English.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Biographical Reference Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources.
Related Material
News Service Biographical Files, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Clippings (information artifacts); Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Employees; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- History; Duke University. University Archives; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Administration
- Biographical Files
  Arrangement note
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Abdelnaby, Alaa (Box 1)
  - Abel, Trudi (Box 1)
  - Abele, Julian F. (Box 1)
  - Abrams, Ian Neal (Box 1)
  - Acomb, Frances [History] (Box 1)
  - Adams, Anne (Box 1)
  - Adams, Donald K. (Box 1)
  - Adams, John Hamilton (Box 1)
  - Adams, Myrna Campbell [V.P. Inst. Equity] (Box 1)
  - Adams, Rex D. [Fuqua Dean] (Box 1)
  - Adcock, David B. (Box 1)
  - Adcock, John F. (Box 1)
  - Addoms, Ruth M. [Botany] (Box 1)
  - Ader, Paul [Author, T '40] (Box 1)
  - Aers, David [English] (Box 1)
  - Aikens, Herbert E. (Box 1)
  - Aitken, P. Wesley (Box 1)
  - Alarie, Mark (Box 1)
  - Alden, John R. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Irving E. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, J. L. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, John Frank (Box 1)
  - Allard, William K. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Gay Wilson (Box 1)
  - Allen, George G. (Box 1)
  - Allen, George V. (Box 1)
  - Alleva, Joe (Box 1)
  - Alspaugh, John W. (Box 1)
  - Alston, Joseph L. (Box 1)
  - Amaker, Tommy [Basketball] (Box 1)
  - Amos, Dennis Bernard (Box 1)
  - Anderson, C. William [Chemistry] (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Carl L. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Charles R. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, David E. (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Hugh (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Jay (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Lewis E. [Botany] (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Roger F. [Forestry] (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Julie Tetel [Prof. of Linguistics] (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Sam (Box 1)
  - Anlyan, Dr. William G.[M.D.] (Box 1)
  - Antepli, Abdullah (Box 1)
  - Antonovics, Janis [Botany] (Box 1)
  - Apgar, Lawrence Clarke (Box 1)
  - Appel, Stanley H. [DUMC] (Box 1)
  - Applewhite, James (Box 1)
  - Apte, Mahadev & Judit-Katona [Anthropology/Nutrition] (Box 1)
  - Arcus, David [Duke Chapel organist] (Box 1)
  - Archie, William Council (Box 1)
  - Arena, Jay (Box 1)
  - Arias, Oscar [President of Costa Rica 1986-1990] (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Dr. Brenda (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Joseph L. (Box 1)
  - Arnett, Edward M. (Box 1)
  - Arpad, Joseph J. (Box 1)
  - Artis, R. Lois (Box 1)
  - Artley, John (Box 1)
  - Ascher, Dr. William (Box 1)
  - Ashmore, Frank [Administration] (Box 1)
  - Atkins, Peter [Greenhouses] (Box 1)
  - Atwater, James (Box 1)
  - Aubery, Pierre L. [Romance Languages] (Box 1)
  - Aumiller, Richard [Drama] (Box 1)
  - Aycock, Charles Brantley (Box 1)
  - Azenberg, Manny (Box 1)
  - Baade, Hans W. (Box 1)
  - Back, Kurt W. (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Joseph [Zoology] (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Lloyd R. [Divinity] (Box 1)
  - Baker, Frank (Box 1)
  - Baker, Lennox Dial [Baker, Virginia] (Box 1)
  - Baker, William (Box 1)
  - Baldwin, Alice Mary (Box 1)
  - Ball, M. Margaret (Box 2)
  - Ball, David [Drama Program] (Box 2)
  - Ballantyne, Robert (Box 2)
  - Bandy, Jim (Box 2)
  - Banham, Katherine (Box 2)
  - Banks, Gene (Box 2)
  - Banner, Leslie (Box 2)
  - Barber, James David [Political Science] (Box 2)
  - Barber, Richard T. [Marine Lab] (Box 2)
  - Barlow, Norman H. [Romance Languages] (Box 2)
  - Barnes, J. Foster (Box 2)
  - Barr, Roger C. [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 2)
  - Barron, Winnie (Box 2)
  - Bartlett, Katharine T. [Law] (Box 2)
  - Bass, Anne & Robert (Box 2)
  - Bassett, John Spencer (Box 2)
  - Bates, Robert H. [Political Science] (Box 2)
  - Battier, Shane, '01 [Basketball - Retired Jersey, #31] (Box 2)
  - Battle, Joseph (Box 2)
  - Baugh, Phillip Jackson (Jack) (Box 2)
  - Baum, Paul Franklin [English] (Box 2)
  - Baylin, George Jay [DUMC] (Box 2)
  - Baylis, Charles A. (Box 2)
  - Bayor, Celal [President of Turkey, Tour of the United States June-March 1954 (visit to N.C., Duke University)] (Box 2)
  - Beach, Waldo (Box 2)
  - Beal, James Allen [Forestry] (Box 2)
  - Beale, Sara Sun [Law] (Box 2)
  - Bear, Warren C. A. [Chief Security Officer] (Box 2)
  - Beatty, Croom (Box 2)
  - Beck, Judy Anna (Box 2)
  - Beckum, Leonard C. [Vice Pres., Vice Provost] (Box 2)
  - Becton, Charles L. (Box 2)
  - Behn, Robert (Box 2)
  - Behrens, Helen Kindler [Author, '43] (Box 2)
  - Beifuss, Joellen (Box 2)
  - Bello, Lou (Box 2)
  - Belvin, James (Box 2)
  - Bender, Bob [Athletics] (Box 2)
  - Bennett, Ben [1984. Football, QB] (Box 2)
  - Bennett, Peter (Box 2)
  - Benson, Danna J. (Box 2)
  - Bergland, John K. (Box 2)
  - Bergman, Judith (Box 2)
  - Bergquist, Charles [History] (Box 2)
  - Bernheim, Frederick (Box 2)
  - Bernheim, Mary Lilias Christian "Molly" [MD] (Box 2)
  - Berninger, Oscar [Dining Halls] (Box 2)
  - Bernstein, Herbert [Law] (Box 2)
  - Bernstein, John [English, Drama] (Box 2)
  - Berry, E. Willard [Geology] (Box 2)
  - Bertozzi, Andrea [Math] (Box 2)
  - Best, Chris & Kim (Box 2)
  - Best, Michael (Box 2)
  - Bethea, Joseph B. (Box 2)
  - Bettman, James R. [Fuqua] (Box 2)
  - Bevan, William (Box 2)
  - Bevington, Helen Smith (Box 2)
  - Bevington, Merle Mowbray [English] (Box 2)
  - Beyel, Joseph S. [Vice Chancellor for Development & Alumni Affairs] (Box 2)
  - Biddle Family (Box 2)
  - Biddle, Anthony Joseph Drexel, Jr. [Mary D. B. T. Semans' father] (Box 2)
  - Biddle, Mary Duke [Mary D. B. T. Semans' mother] (Box 2)
  - Biddle, Nicholas Duke [Mary D. B. T. Semans' brother] (Box 2)
  - Biedenharn, Lawrence C. [Physics] (Box 2)
  - Bierman, Alan [Computer Science] (Box 2)
  - Bigelow, Lucius Arelius [Chemistry] (Box 2)
  - Bilas, Jay [Basketball] (Box 2)
  - Billings, William Dwight "Dwight" [Botany] (Box 2)
  - Bilpuch, Edward G. (Box 2)
  - Bindewald, Richard A. (Box 2)
  - Binkley, Daniel E. [Forestry] (Box 2)
  - Bird, Warren Phillip [Med. Ctr. Library] (Box 2)
  - Birkhead, Clarence (Box 2)
  - Biswas, Moy (Box 2)
  - Bivens, J. F. [Trinity Park School] (Box 2)
  - Black, Martin Lee, Jr. [Accounting] (Box 3)
  - Blackburn, John O. (Box 3)
  - Blackburn, William Maxwell [English] (Box 3)
  - Blake, Bob (Box 3)
  - Blake, J. Donald (Box 3)
  - Blakely, Florence E. [Librarian] (Box 3)
  - Bland, Kalman [Religion] (Box 3)
  - Blaydon, Colin [Administration] (Box 3)
  - Block, Herbert (Box 3)
  - Blomquist, Hugo L. [Botany] (Box 3)
  - Blomquist, Margaret [wife of Hugo Blomquist; daughter of Samuel Fox Mordecai] (Box 3)
  - Bloom, David P. (Box 3)
  - Bloomquist, Karen (Box 3)
  - Blue, Daniel Terry, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Blumenfeld, Donald [Dance] (Box 3)
  - Bly, James R. "Jim" (Box 3)
  - Boatwright, Mary T. [Classical Studies] (Box 3)
  - Bock, Karl (Box 3)
  - Boger, John Charles (Box 3)
  - Bolich, William Bryan [Law] (Box 3)
  - Bolmeier, Edward C. [Education] (Box 3)
  - Bonaventura, Joseph & Celia (Box 3)
  - Bonawit, G. Owen (Box 3)
  - Bone, Allan H. [Music] (Box 3)
  - Bonk, James F. [Chemistry] (Box 3)
  - Bookout, Cazlyn G. [Marine Lab] (Box 3)
  - Bookout, Dr. Elizabeth [Women's Phys. Ed.] (Box 3)
  - Boomer, Walter E. '60 [Marine Lt. General] (Box 3)
  - Boone, Sam [D. U. Library] (Box 3)
  - Booth, Rachel Z. [Nursing] (Box 3)
  - Boothby, Neil (Box 3)
  - Borchardt, Frank [German] (Box 3)
  - Bornes, John (Box 3)
  - Borstelmann, Lloyd J. (Box 3)
  - Bosley, Harold A. [Divinity] (Box 3)
  - Bossoms, Bob [Football] (Box 3)
  - Boulware, Dr. Caldwell Elwood (Box 3)
  - Boumpani, Neil [DUMB] (Box 3)
  - Bowers, Henry Franklin (Box 3)
  - Bowles, Charles Phillips (Box 3)
  - Bowman, Francis E. [English] (Box 3)
  - Bowyer, Kevin [Computer Science] (Box 3)
  - Boyce, Benjamin [English] (Box 3)
  - Boyce, Stephen G. [Forestry] (Box 3)
  - Boyd, Robert (Box 3)
  - Boyd, Julian P. (Box 3)
  - Boyd, William Kenneth [History] (Box 3)
  - Bradford, William D. [Pathology] (Box 3)
  - Bradley, David Gilbert [Religion] (Box 3)
  - Bradley, Harold "Hal" [Basketball Coach] (Box 3)
  - Bradway, John S. [Law] (Box 3)
  - Bradsher, Charles K. [Chemistry] (Box 3)
  - Braibanti, Ralph [Political Science], [3 folders] (Box 3)
  - Brannon, Anthony M. (Box 3)
  - Branscom, B. Harvie (Box 3)
  - Branscom, Lewis (Box 3)
  - Branson, Anna [Anna Branson Thomas] (Box 3)
  - Branson, Barbara [Librarian] (Box 3)
  - Brantley, B. Alton, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Brazzel, Debra (Box 3)
  - Breeden, Doug [Fuqua] (Box 3)
  - Breedlove, Joseph Penn [Librarian] (Box 3)
  - Brees, Anton [Carillonneur, Bok Tower & Duke] (Box 3)
  - Bressler, Bernard (Box 3)
  - Brewer, James H. (Box 4)
  - Brewer, Pierce Oliver "Kidd" (Box 4)
  - Brewer, Nicholas (Box 4)
  - Brice, Ashbel G. [Director, Duke Univ. Press] (Box 4)
  - Bridges, Furman A. [Languages] (Box 4)
  - Brill, Bill '52 (Box 4)
  - Briner, William H. [Radiology & Radiopharmacy] (Box 4)
  - Brinkhous, John (Box 4)
  - Brinkley, Dean R. Florence (Box 4)
  - Broadfoot, Winston (Box 4)
  - Brock, Dorothy Pendle "Dot" (Box 4)
  - Broderson, Robert [Art] (Box 4)
  - Brodhead, Bob (Box 4)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H. [President]
    - Inauguration, Sept, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Presidential term (Box 4)
    - Speech file (Box 4)
  - Brodie, H. Keith H. [Psychiatry, Chancellor] (Box 4)
  - Brodie, Brenda (Box 4)
  - Brondoli, Michael (Box 4)
  - Bronfenbrenner, Martin [Economics] (Box 4)
  - Brooks, Eugene Clyde (Box 4)
  - Broughton, Annie Leigh (Box 4)
  - Brower, Alfred Smith [Administration] (Box 4)
  - Brower, James F. (Box 4)
  - Brower, Lewis M. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Charlotte Vestal [Art] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Earl II [Engineering] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Frances C. (Box 4)
  - Brown, Frank Clyde [English] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Ivan W. [Pathology, Surgery] (Box 4)
  - Brown, J. Trig [Medicine] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Joseph Gill (Box 4)
  - Brown, Les (Box 4)
  - Brown, Myrtle Irene [Nursing] (Box 4)
  - Brown, Noel (Box 4)
  - Brummett, Paul [Director of Supplies] (Box 4)
  - Bruton, John Fletcher [Trustee] (Box 4)
  - Bruzelius, Caroline Astrid [Art] (Box 4)
  - Bryan, Anne-Marie (Box 4)
  - Bryan, Joseph M. & Kathleen Price (Box 4)
  - Bryan, Paul R., Jr. [Music] (Box 4)
  - Bryan, Virginia S. [Administration, Botany] (Box 4)
  - Bryers, James D. (Box 4)
  - Bryson, Edwin C. [Administration] (Box 4)
  - Bubas, Vic (Box 4)
  - Buckner, Carl (Box 4)
  - Budd, Louis J. [English] (Box 4)
  - Buehler, Albert [Track coach] (Box 4)
  - Buettner-Janusch, John [Anthropology, Anatomy, Zoology (Box 4)
  - Bullard, Betty Moore [Asia Society, New York] (Box 4)
  - Bullard, Scott (Box 4)
  - Burford, Walter [Religion] (Box 4)
  - Burger, Paula Phillips (Box 4)
  - Burke, Delores (Box 4)
  - Burness, John F. [Sr. V. P. for Public Affairs] (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Carol (Box 4)
  - Burnette, Brenda (Box 4)
  - Burns, Richard (Box 4)
  - Burr, Bettz Taylor ['61, Novelist] (Box 4)
  - Burr, Raymond (Box 4)
  - Burton, Richard M. (Box 4)
  - Buschman, Barbara (Box 4)
  - Busse, Dr. Ewald W. [Psychiatry] (Box 4)
  - Butterfield, Barbara Sale [Human Resources] (Box 4)
  - Butters, Ron [English] (Box 5)
  - Butters, Tom [Athletics] (Box 5)
  - Byrd, Robert L. [Manuscripts] (Box 5)
  - Cady, Edwin H. [Humanities] (Box 5)
  - Cahow, Clark [Administration] (Box 5)
  - Caldwell, Herschel [Football Coach] (Box 5)
  - Calero, Adolfo (Box 5)
  - Calkins, Phillip [History] (Box 5)
  - Callaway, J. Lamar, M.D. (Box 5)
  - Callaway, Laine [Divinity] (Box 5)
  - Cameron, Edmund M. "Eddie" [Athletics] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Dennis M. [Divinity] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Jerry Dean [Librarian] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Richard T. [Sociology] (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Thomas (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Will [Divinity] (Box 5)
  - Canada, Mary [Librarian] (Box 5)
  - Cannon, Charles A. [Trustee] (Box 5)
  - Cannon, James, III [Dean, Divinity School] (Box 5)
  - Cannon, Taffy (Box 5)
  - Cannon, William Ragsdale (Box 5)
  - Carbone, Peter [Education] (Box 5)
  - Card, Wilbur Wade "Cap" (Box 5)
  - Carlson, Cathy [Duke University Chaplain] (Box 5)
  - Carlton, John W. [Divinity] (Box 5)
  - Carpenter, David Williams [Physics] (Box 5)
  - Carr, Jean [Gardens] (Box 5)
  - Carr, John W., Jr. [Education] (Box 5)
  - Carr, Julian S. (Box 5)
  - Carrington, Paul D. [Law] (Box 5)
  - Caroll, Eber Malcolm [History] (Box 5)
  - Carswell, G. Harold (Box 5)
  - Carter, James H. [Psychiatry] (Box 5)
  - Cartmill, Matt [Anatomy] (Box 5)
  - Cartter, Dr. Allan M. (Box 5)
  - Cartwright, William H. (Box 5)
  - Carver, Roy J. [Investor] (Box 5)
  - Casey, H. Craig [Engineering] (Box 5)
  - Cauce, Cesar (Box 5)
  - Cavanagh, George Stanley Terrance "Terry" (Box 5)
  - Kyle Cavanaugh [Vice President for Human Resources] (Box 5)
  - Cell, Hohn W. "Jack" [History] (Box 5)
  - Cerveris, Michael [Institute of the Arts] (Box 5)
  - Chaddock, Jack B. [Engineering] (Box 5)
  - Chafe, William G. [History] Chafe, Lorna (Box 5)
  - Chafe, Lorna (Box 5)
  - Chaffin, Nora C. (Box 5)
  - Chaiken, Leon Edward (Box 5)
  - Chambers, Robert L. (Box 5)
  - Champagne, Mary T. [School of Nursing] (Box 5)
  - Chandler, Dr. Arthur [Sports] (Box 5)
  - Chandler, John W. (Box 5)
  - Chandler, Linda [Author] (Box 5)
  - Chandor, Douglas [Artist] (Box 5)
  - Chappell, Fred [Author] (Box 5)
  - Charette, Leo [Dir., Career Dev. Center] (Box 5)
  - Charlesworth, James H. [Religion] (Box 5)
  - Chavis, Ben [Divinity School; Wilmington 10] (Box 5)
  - Cheasty, Denise (See: Photographs, Activities. Foreign Exchange & Foreign Students) (Box 5)
  - Cheek, Roma Sawyer [Poly Sci] (Box 5)
  - Chesnut, Paul I. [Library] (Box 5)
  - Childs, Benjamin Guy (Box 5)
  - Chretien, Jean [Canadian Prime Minister] (Box 5)
  - Christ, Robert W. [Library] (Box 5)
  - Christakos, Arthur [Dean, Undergraduate Med Education] (Box 5)
  - Christenson, Norman L. [Botany] (Box 5)
  - Ciompi, Arturo (Box 5)
  - Ciompi, Giorgio [Violinist] (Box 5)
  - Clack, Jim (Box 6)
  - Clark, Elizabeth Ann [Religion] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Elon [Medical Art & Illustration] (Box 6)
  - Clark, George [Football] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Henry B. [Religion] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Howard G. [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Kenneth W. [Divinity] (Box 6)
  - Clark, Thomas D. (Box 6)
  - Clarke-Pearson, Daniel [Medical] (Box 6)
  - Cleaveland, Frederic N. [Political Science, Administration] (Box 6)
  - Cleland, James T. [Duke Chapel]
    - CV, Writings, Tributes (Box 6)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 6)
    - Memorial Articles, Programs/Services [Alice Mead Cleland] (Box 6)
  - Cleland, William [Medical Center] (Box 6)
  - Cleveland, Louise (Box 6)
  - Clifford, Paul [Art Museum] (Box 6)
  - Clotfelter, Charles T. (Box 6)
  - Clum, John M. [English] (Box 6)
  - Clyde, Mary Kestler (Box 6)
  - Clyde, Paul H. [History, Administration] (Box 6)
  - Cocke, Norman A. [Trustee, Chariman of Board] (Box 6)
  - Cocks, Franklin [Engineering] (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Carolyn [Engineering] (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Harvey J. [Center for Aging] (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Kal (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Kissandra [1996 Graduate] (Box 6)
  - Coile, Theodore [Forestry] (Box 6)
  - Coker, Jerry [Music] (Box 6)
  - Cole, Anne [Three Arts Club] (Box 6)
  - Cole, Arthur Vance [1905] (Box 6)
  - Cole, R. Taylor [Political Science] (Box 6)
  - Coles, Robert [Psychiatry] (Box 6)
  - Colton, Joel [History] (Box 6)
  - Como, Perry (Box 6)
  - Conant, Norman F. [Biology] (Box 6)
  - Connery, Robert H. (Box 6)
  - Connolly, John (Box 6)
  - Constantinescu, Emil [Romanian Geologist] (Box 6)
  - Cook, Emma [1934] (Box 6)
  - Cook, Philip J. [Economics} (Box 6)
  - Cook, Samuel DuBois [Political Science] (Box 6)
  - Cooke, Miriam [Islamic & Judaic Studies] (Box 6)
  - Coombs, John Wesley [Baseball] (Box 6)
  - Coon, Susan L. [Cultural Affairs] (Box 6)
  - Cooper, Walter G. [Personnel Director; V-12 Commanding Officer] (Box 6)
  - Corbin, Charlotte (Box 6)
  - Corless, Roger J. [Religion] (Box 6)
  - Corrie, Bruce A. (Box 6)
  - Corrigan, Gene (Box 6)
  - Costlow, John [Director of Marine Lab] (Box 6)
  - Cotton, William (Box 6)
  - Couch, Louise [Housing] (Box 6)
  - Covi, Dario Allessandro [Art] (Box 6)
  - Cox, J. Elwood (Box 6)
  - Cox, James D. [Law] (Box 6)
  - Cox, Mary [Math/Physics Library] (Box 6)
  - Cox, Richard L. [Associate VP for Student Affairs and Dean for University Life] (Box 6)
  - Cox, Robert Boyd (Box 6)
  - Cox, Robert C. [Physical Education] (Box 6)
  - Crane, Robert I. [South Asian Program] (Box 6)
  - Cranford, William Ivey [1891] (Box 6)
  - Craven, James Braxton, Jr. [Trustee] (Box 6)
  - Craven, Braxton (Box 6)
  - Craven, Braxton - - Genealogy (Box 6)
  - Craven, Leslie [Law Faculty] (Box 6)
  - Craven, Wesley Frank (Box 6)
  - Crawford, Fred [Football] (Box 6)
  - Creasman, William R. [Med. Center OB-GYN] (Box 6)
  - Creech, Frank [Artmaker] (Box 6)
  - Crenshaw, James L. [Divinity] (Box 6)
  - Crenshaw, Hugh Charles [Zoology] (Box 6)
  - Crenshaw, Wanda [Employee] (Box 6)
  - Crotwell, Helen [Divinity] (Box 6)
  - Cross, Peggy [DSG] (Box 6)
  - Crovitz, Elaine K. [Medical] (Box 6)
  - Crowder, Max [Trainer] (Box 7)
  - Crowell, John Franklin [Trinity College President] (Box 7)
  - Crum, Mason [Biblical Literature] (Box 7)
  - Crumbliss, Alvin L. [Chemistry] (Box 7)
  - Culberson, William Louis [Botany] (Box 7)
  - Cullen, Tony [Lacrosse Coach] (Box 7)
  - Cummings, Maj. Edwin F., Jr. (Box 7)
  - Cunningham, Bruce [Registrar] (Box 7)
  - Curtin, Philip D. (Box 7)
  - Curtis, Mike (Box 7)
  - Curtiss, John S. [History] (Box 7)
  - Cushman, Robert E. (& Barbara) [Divinity] (Box 7)
  - Cutter, Bowman, W. (Box 7)
  - Dalton, Harry L. [1916] (Box 7)
  - Daly, Charles J. "Chuck" (Box 7)
  - Darkis, Frederick R. (Box 7)
  - Darling, Marsha (Box 7)
  - D'Armi, Tom [Baseball] (Box 7)
  - Davenport, Guy [1948; Poet] (Box 7)
  - Davidson, Clint [VP for Human Resources] (Box 7)
  - Davidson, Cathy (Box 7)
  - Davies, David G. [Economics] (Box 7)
  - Davies, Robert N. (Box 7)
  - Davies, W. D. [Divinity] (Box 7)
  - Davis, Burke [Author] (Box 7)
  - Davis, Calvin [History] (Box 7)
  - Davis, Chuck (Box 7)
  - Davis, Gifford [Romance Languages] (Box 7)
  - Davis, Lawrence "Crash" [Baseball] (Box 7)
  - Davis, Lucy Tolbert (Box 7)
  - Davison, Wilburt Cornell
    - Publications (Box 7)
    - Symposium on the Commonwealth of Children (Box 7)
  - Dawkins, Johnny [Basketball - Retired Jersey, #24] (Box 7)
  - Dawson, Lois Deloatch (Box 7)
  - Day, Eugene (Box 7)
  - Day, Ruth [Psychology] (Box 7)
  - Dean, Robert [DUPD] (Box 7)
  - Deane, Disque D. (Box 7)
  - Dees, John & Susan (Box 7)
  - DeHart, Jimmy [Football] (Box 7)
  - DeJong, David Cornel [Novelist] (Box 7)
  - Dellinger, David C. [Business] (Box 7)
  - Dellinger, Walter E., III [Law] (Box 7)
  - DeLuca, John (Box 7)
  - DeMik, Harry (Box 7)
  - DeMott, Deborah A. [Law Faculty] (Box 7)
  - DeNardis, Rebecca (Box 7)
  - DeNeef, A. Leigh [English] (Box 7)
  - Dennis, John S. [Maintenance Dept.] (Box 7)
  - DeVries, Walter [Political Science] (Box 7)
  - DeVries, William [Surgeon] (Box 7)
  - DeVyver, Frank T. [Economics] (Box 7)
  - Diamond, I. T. [Biological Psychology] (Box 7)
  - Dibona, Joseph [Education] (Box 7)
  - Dickens, Robert L. [Administration] (Box 7)
  - Dickerson, Janet [Student Affairs] (Box 7)
  - Dicks, Russell L. [Divinity School] (Box 7)
  - Dickson, Sally M. (Box 7)
  - Di Corcia, Joseph [History] (Box 7)
  - Dillon, Judy [Office of Research Support] (Box 7)
  - DiMona, Joseph [1947] (Box 7)
  - Diosegy, Arlene [Asst. Univ. Counsel for Health Affairs] (Box 7)
  - Dirlik, Arif [History] (Box 7)
  - Dittmann, Jane (Box 7)
  - Dixon, Thomas E. (Box 7)
  - Dolan, Margaret B. [American Public Health Association] (Box 8)
  - Dole, Elizabeth Hanford, '58
    - 1958-1975 (Box 8)
    - 1975-1986 (Box 8)
    - 1987-1998 (Box 8)
    - 1999- (Box 8)
    - Women of Achievement (Box 8)
  - Dominquez, Virginia [Anthropology] (Box 8)
  - Donnelly, John [Stonecarvers] (Box 8)
  - Dorfman, Ariel (Box 8)
  - Doub Family (Box 8)
  - Doub, Peter (Box 8)
  - Douglas, Fenner (Box 8)
  - Douthat, James [Administration] (Box 8)
  - Dover, Hugh C. [Language Lab] (Box 8)
  - Dow, Alden B. (Box 8)
  - Dow, Marie Therese Liniere [French] and Dow, Neal [French] (Box 8)
  - Dowd Jerome (Box 8)
  - Dowell, David [Librarian] (Box 8)
  - Dowell, Earl [Engineering] (Box 8)
  - Dozier, John M. [Administration] (Box 8)
  - Dressel, Francis G. [Math] (Box 8)
  - Drew, Thomas L. [Assistant Dean, Fuqua School of Business] (Box 8)
  - Driesell, Lefty (Box 8)
  - Drill, Isobel Craven Lewis '37 [Great-grandaughter of Braxton Craven] (Box 8)
  - Dudley, Trevania D. '80 (Box 8)
  - Duffy, Bernard [English] (Box 8)
  - Duke, A. St. George Biddle "Pony" (Box 8)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 8)
  - Duke, Angier Buchanan (Box 8)
  - Duke, Anthony Drexel "Tony" (Box 8)
  - Duke, Benjamin Newton
    - Biographical (Box 8)
    - Memorials, Tributes, etc. (Box 8)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 8)
  - Duke, Brodie Leonidas (Box 8)
  - Duke, Doris
    - Nov. 22, 1912-Oct. 25, 1993 [d. 10-28-1993] (Box 8)
    - Oct. 28, 1993- (Box 9)
    - Lengthy articles (Box 9)
  - Duke Family
    - Genealogy (Box 9)
    - Individuals [Various]. See also: Biddle; Semans (Box 9)
    - Philanthropy and Donations (Box 9)
  - Duke, James B.
    - Origins of the American Tobacco Company (Box 9)
    - Articles, 1924-1964 (Box 9)
    - Articles, 1968- (Box 9)
    - Bibliographies (Box 9)
    - Biographies (Box 9)
    - Death and Memorials (Box 9)
    - Determination by the Executors of James B. Duke, Deceased (Box 9)
    - The Duke Endowment (Box 9)
    - Eastman National Business College, NY (Box 9)
    - Final Illness (Box 9)
    - Politics and Prosperity, 1915 (Box 9)
  - Duke, Nanaline Lee Holt Inman (Box 9)
  - Duke, Robin Chandler (Box 10)
  - Duke, Taylor (Box 10)
  - Duke, Washington
    - Biographical material (Box 10)
    - American Tobacco Company (Box 10)
    - Newspaper Articles (Box 10)
  - Duke, William James "Uncle Billie" (Box 10)
  - Dukes, Charles A. (Box 10)
  - Dula, William C. (Box 10)
  - Dumas, Paul (Box 10)
  - Duncan, Exie [Duke Press] (Box 10)
  - Dunlap, Connie R. (Box 10)
  - Dunn, Susan [Music] (Box 10)
  - Dupree, Louis [Islamic and Arabian Development Studies] (Box 10)
  - DuRant, Edward Wilson [NROTC] (Box 10)
  - Durden, Robert Franklin [History] (Box 10)
  - Durham, Plato T. (Box 10)
  - Dutrow, George F. [Forestry] (Box 10)
  - Dwire, Henry Rudolph (Box 10)
  - Dyba, Johannes [German Archbishop] (Box 10)
  - Dzau, Victor (Box 10)
  - Eagle, Watt Weems [MD] (Box 10)
  - Easley, Eleanor [Duke Medical School & Medical Center] (Box 10)
  - Easley, Howard [Education] (Box 10)
  - Eastman, George (Box 10)
  - Eban, Abba (Box 10)
  - Eceuit, Bulent [Turkish Premier. Visitor July 1976] (Box 10)
  - Edens, A. Hollis [President] (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Charles Williams [Physics] (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Drew [Medical Center] (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Herbert O. [Divinity] (Box 10)
  - Edwards, Joseph Phillip [Engineering] (Box 10)
  - Efird, James M. [Divinity] (Box 10)
  - Egeli, Cedric (Box 10)
  - Ehlhardt, George Brinkman [Divinity] (Box 10)
  - Eidenier, Elon G. "Jerry" [Poet] (Box 10)